Hello friends, are you friends, this is the
second product of Health Insurance Products Part 2, in which
you have to pay very less premium and
you get a lot of coverage, in which you can get a sum of Rs
50 lakh for Rs 12,000, an
individual can get a sum of Rs 50 lakh for Rs 18,000,
in this you get all kinds of features which are extra and
not so features, like
hospital catch benefit, cash outpatient department,
global coverage which you get and
in this you also get an ambulance, along with this, it is
such a product in which
you will get loyalty discount as you
increase, in
which you will get discount
on your premium, secondly, in this you
also get coverage of unlimited non-medical expenses, which is very important to have
in a new product nowadays, and there are
other
features in it, so the number for this is
given, you can call me
on any type of console of any help
me and you can contact me, thank you